<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harrow Health Matters</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Harrow Health Matters</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Varsha Soneji - Vanaspati Herbal Medicine</title>
      <link>/vanaspati/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vanaspati/</guid>
      <description>Varsha is a Medical Herbalist with over 31 years of experience in the field of complementary medicine and a degree in Herbal Medicine. She has vast knowledge of:
 Western Herbs Indian and Ayurvedic Herbs Chinese Herbs  Varsha’s knowledge of these 3 areas of herbalism, is combined to maximise the benefits of the phytochemicals (natural plant chemicals) that nature has given to us packaged as beautiful plants. She offers private health consultations in her Stanmore clinic and via video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brian Jacobs - Hypnotherapist</title>
      <link>/brian_jacobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/brian_jacobs/</guid>
      <description>Brian Jacobs is a registered clinical hypnotherapist, as well as a hypnotherapy trainer. He has been in practice for 20 years and has offices in Finchley Central (in North London) as well as in Harley Street (Central London). He sees clients to help them with behavioural change (for example, help to stop smoking, control weight, stop nail biting) and emotional change (including reducing fears and anxiety, overcoming phobias, and gaining confidence).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jill Swyers - Hippocrates Health Institute</title>
      <link>/jill_swyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jill_swyers/</guid>
      <description>Jill has worked in the food industry for more than 40 years, having worked in hotels, restaurants and events catering in various countries round the world, as well as running her own successful London-based catering company.
She is a qualified Hippocrates Health Educator since 1998, and currently teaches and demonstrates the preparation of PlantBased Living Foods with a Balance of Nutrition.
As a Teacher, Consultant and Chef, Jill&amp;rsquo;s main priority is Food Literacy – just because it is PlantBased does not necessarily mean it is healthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lalit Sodha - Chiropractor</title>
      <link>/lalit_sodha/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lalit_sodha/</guid>
      <description>With 30 years of clinical experience in private practice, and having treated thousands of patients, not only in the UK, but across the globe, Lalit Sodha D.C, believes in his mission statement of ‘Health by choice, and not by chance’.
His practice in Eastcote hosts a well-trained team of Chiropractors, Osteopaths, Massage Therapists, and a brilliant support team (who are the life of the clinic!). With a warm and welcoming atmosphere, every patient is treated like a member of the family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manish Gohel - Master NLP Practitioner, Trainer, Coach, Yoga Instructor and Reiki Master</title>
      <link>/manish_gohel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/manish_gohel/</guid>
      <description>Manish is a highly experienced and knowledgeable Coach. His passion is to provide the very best for his clients.
As a Master NLP Practitioner &amp;amp; Trainer and a certified Marshall Goldsmith Executive Coach, he provides the necessary techniques and tools to get the very best out of his clients, with a secure and confidential environment. He has a personal passion and desire to ensure that his clients get the very best of themselves from every coaching session, as well as continued ongoing self-growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rakhee Shah - Holistic Therapist</title>
      <link>/rakhee_shah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rakhee_shah/</guid>
      <description>Rakhee Shah is a holistic therapist, who gained her qualifications over 20 years ago. She practices reflexology, aromatherapy and has completed the British nutrition foundation course. She likes to help and inspire people to achieve optimal balance in order to live a higher quality of life.
She does home visits and provides an initial face-to-face consultation and one-to-one session. She enjoys healthy cooking and eating, and gaining more knowledge and understanding about the right nutrition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sara Cordell - Massage Therapist &amp; Aromatherapist</title>
      <link>/sara_cordell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sara_cordell/</guid>
      <description>Sara qualified as a licenced massage therapist and aromatherapist in 1996 when she realised her calling in life and started on her journey to make a difference in people’s lives by putting her energy into learning advanced techniques to enable her to rid , or help people, diminish their pains.
She has taught advanced and basic massage and has done various talks, and gives back by teaching what she’s discovered to those starting out their journeys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bhoomi Thaker</title>
      <link>/bhoomi_thaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bhoomi_thaker/</guid>
      <description>Bhoomi Thaker is Harrow based Usui traditional Reiki Master teacher. Bhoomi has been practicing Reiki for 13 years.
As a Reiki Master Teacher, Bhoomi takes pride in teaching her students the traditional art of self healing.
With her experience of Reiki, she not only heals the physical ailment but work on deep routes issues, casing the physical ailments. Her treatments are bespoke and fit most needs.
Apart from being a Reiki healer, Bhoomi also works with crystals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charul Bakhda</title>
      <link>/charul_bakhda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/charul_bakhda/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinar Abdulaziz - Creative Counsellor and Workshop Facilitator</title>
      <link>/chinar_abdulaziz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/chinar_abdulaziz/</guid>
      <description>Chinar is a Creative Counsellor and Workshop Facilitator helping to empower individuals to see they have options and choices to have a more fulfilling life. She is based in West London. During the lockdown, she&amp;rsquo;s been doing her workshops online. Her workshops are for adults – mainly women between the ages 35-65 although she does have men coming along from time to time.
You may get in touch with Chinar at:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esther Shortt</title>
      <link>/esther_shortt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/esther_shortt/</guid>
      <description>I am fully qualified to teach exercise to music and level 4 Yoga teacher, BWY trained. Fully insured to teach you, with lots of experience, I am a Cimspa Member.
I am running a full programme of online classes, all my classes can be accessed via Zoom and I run a range of classes, from Yoga, pilates, dance, LBT and Zumba and much more, I will be offering a selection of classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennie Alexander</title>
      <link>/jennie_alexander/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jennie_alexander/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Morris</title>
      <link>/lisa_morris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lisa_morris/</guid>
      <description>Lisa teaches Iyengar yoga from a purpose-built specialist studio in Bushey Heath, near Watford, Hertfordshire. During 2020 Lisa has been teaching online and has been welcoming yoga students to class from all over the UK and beyond! She invites you into her beautiful little tranquil garden space, set under an old oak and beside the green belt fields of Bushey. Learn more about healing yourself through this clever systematic ancient technology, with a focus on alignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mahesh Shah</title>
      <link>/mahesh_shah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mahesh_shah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nirmala Iyer</title>
      <link>/nirmala_iyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nirmala_iyer/</guid>
      <description>Profile of Nirmala Iyer I started my Yoga Journey a little over a decade ago and after 4 years of practicing as a student, I wanted to deepen my understanding of Yoga as a therapeutic way of life, egged on by the lower back pain that a few family members (across age groups) were dealing with! I completed my International Yoga Teachers Training Certificate under my Yoga Guru, Pundit Radheshyam Mishra from Yoga Life Global India.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosalie Segal</title>
      <link>/rosalie_segal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rosalie_segal/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sal Batavia</title>
      <link>/sal_batavia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sal_batavia/</guid>
      <description>After a 20-year career as a Social Worker and Counsellor Sal Batavia runs a successful holistic wellness practice in London. All her services are also available remotely to clients that a further afield / during the CV19 pandemic. Sal currently offers the services of Craniosacral Therapy; &amp;lsquo;Hands-On Hands-Off&amp;rsquo; Remote Body Therapy; Past Life Transformational Regression Therapy; Inner Child and Current Life Transformational Regression Therapy; Energy Attachment Release Therapy. The first two services are suitable for pregnancy, babies, children, teenagers and everyone else in the family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shabari Monica Das - Green Beauty Lifestyle Consultant</title>
      <link>/shabari_monica_das/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shabari_monica_das/</guid>
      <description>Shabari Das is a Green Beauty Lifestyle Consultant.
You know how a lot of people, especially during the current situation, are thinking about the impact of their choices but don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do or where to start.
Shabari helps people who would like to live a greener, healthier, more compassionate, and ethical lifestyle by advising them on what changes they can make, what to look out for and what to avoid, and assisting them in choosing natural, chemical-free, vegan, eco-friendly, and cruelty-free products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Varsha Hathi</title>
      <link>/varsha_hathi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/varsha_hathi/</guid>
      <description>Divorce &amp;amp; Confidence Coach, empowers and supports women who are either contemplating divorce, or already on that path. Providing them with a mechanism that is simple, honest, and caring.
As we know, leaving a marriage is no way an easy option, for some it will seem impossible to do, let alone making the decision.
The reality is that it is possible, with the right support structure, that is where Varsha Hathi comes in, she is with you each step of the journey.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
